[
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sabaton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Cardigans", 
      "Babymetal", 
      "Scorpions", 
      "Millencolin", 
      "Alcazar", 
      "Ace of Base", 
      "Blind Guardian", 
      "Manowar", 
      "Dark Tranquillity", 
      "Bathory"
    ], 
    "question": "'Heroes' was an album by which Swedish heavy metal band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Queen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals"
    ], 
    "question": "'Roger Taylor' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Elvis Costello", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Elton John", 
      "Bob Dylan", 
      "Bono"
    ], 
    "question": "Who In The World Of Music Was Born With The Name \"Declan McManus\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Offspring", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Styx", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Jefferson Airplane", 
      "LMFAO", 
      "Static-X", 
      "P.O.D.", 
      "Hoobastank", 
      "The Doobie Brothers", 
      "Allman Brothers Band"
    ], 
    "question": "'Rise and Fall, Rage and Grace' was a studio album by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Led Zeppelin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Lostprophets", 
      "The Kinks", 
      "King Crimson", 
      "Whitesnake", 
      "Gorillaz", 
      "Kaiser Chiefs", 
      "Jethro Tull", 
      "The Yardbirds", 
      "Venom"
    ], 
    "question": "'John Paul Jones' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Weather Report", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Drowning Pool", 
      "Hole", 
      "Type O Negative"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Band Was Formed In The 1970's By Fomer Miles Davis Band Members Joe Zawinul & Wayne Shorter?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Coldplay", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals"
    ], 
    "question": "'Parachutes' was a studio album by which British band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Rolling Stones", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "McFly", 
      "Delirious?", 
      "Depeche Mode", 
      "All Saints", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "One Direction", 
      "Fairport Convention", 
      "Thompson Twins", 
      "Tears for Fears", 
      "Il Divo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Bill Wyman'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Glen Miller", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jack Acres", 
      "Laurence Ransom", 
      "Mark Bosworth"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The Musical Major Whose Plane Dissapeared Somewhere Over The English Channel In December 1944", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Placebo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Magnum", 
      "Kaiser Chiefs", 
      "Jethro Tull", 
      "The Yardbirds", 
      "Venom", 
      "Sugababes", 
      "Noel Gallagher's High Flying Birds", 
      "Mot\u00f6rhead", 
      "Jamiroquai", 
      "Cream"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band performed the compilation album 'Once More with Feeling: Singles 1996\u20132004'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nine Inch Nails", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "In This Moment", 
      "Nitty Gritty Dirt Band", 
      "Animal Collective", 
      "Mastodon", 
      "Poco", 
      "Ha*Ash", 
      "Poison", 
      "Avenged Sevenfold", 
      "Live", 
      "Incubus"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1988 includes 'Atticus Ross'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ace Of Base", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Modern Talking", 
      "The Cardigans", 
      "Every Little Thing", 
      "Dream", 
      "Blue System", 
      "Matia Bazar"
    ], 
    "question": "Jenny & Lyn Beggren Are Singers With Which 90's Group", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kate Bush", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "David Bowie", 
      "John Lennon", 
      "George Michael", 
      "James Blunt", 
      "Ozzy Osbourne", 
      "Phil Collins", 
      "Bonnie Tyler", 
      "Ellie Goulding", 
      "Donovan", 
      "Ed Sheeran"
    ], 
    "question": "'December Will Be Magic Again / Warm And Soothing' was a single by which British recording artist, singer, songwriter, musician and record producer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Metallica", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alice Cooper", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "LCD Soundsystem", 
      "Skid Row", 
      "Queensr\u00ffche", 
      "The Monkees", 
      "Scissor Sisters", 
      "Black Flag"
    ], 
    "question": "'Lars Ulrich' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "MC Hammer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vanilla Ice", 
      "Snoop Dogg", 
      "Sir Mix-a-Lot"
    ], 
    "question": "Stanley Burrell Is The Real Name Of Which Popular 90's Musician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Bowie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Mika", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "Robbie Williams", 
      "Ed Sheeran", 
      "Kate Bush", 
      "Joe Cocker", 
      "Mark Knopfler", 
      "John Lennon"
    ], 
    "question": "'Under Pressure' was a song by which British musician, actor, record producer and arranger?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Black Eyed Peas", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Shinedown", 
      "Fleetwood Mac", 
      "Cheap Trick", 
      "Red Hot Chili Peppers", 
      "Chevelle", 
      "Sweetbox"
    ], 
    "question": "'will.i.am' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Uptight", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Upright", 
      "All Night", 
      "Alright"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was The First Top Twenty Hit In The Uk For Stevie Wonder?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Beyonc\u00e9", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madonna", 
      "Drake", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Neil Young", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Thal\u00eda", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Janet Jackson", 
      "Moby"
    ], 
    "question": "'Dangerously in Love' was a studio album by which American singer, actress and record producer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bee Gees", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Culture Club", 
      "Dire Straits", 
      "Saxon", 
      "Pulp", 
      "The Stone Roses", 
      "Roxy Music", 
      "Stereolab", 
      "Simply Red", 
      "Massive Attack"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1958 includes 'Maurice Gibb'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Banjo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fiddle", 
      "Ukelele", 
      "Accordion"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The Guitar Like Instrument With A Circular Belly Of Streched Parchment", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Simon & Garfunkel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "REO Speedwagon", 
      "Lifehouse", 
      "The Temptations", 
      "The Used", 
      "Kool & The Gang", 
      "New Found Glory"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band released the song 'Mrs. Robinson'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Green Day", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mastodon", 
      "Animal Collective", 
      "Fall Out Boy", 
      "Nitty Gritty Dirt Band", 
      "Dropkick Murphys", 
      "Marilyn Manson", 
      "M\u00f6tley Cr\u00fce", 
      "L.A. Guns", 
      "The Mothers of Invention", 
      "Jefferson Airplane"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Billie Joe Armstrong'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Best Shot", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rhythm Stick", 
      "Lovin'", 
      "Poison Arrow"
    ], 
    "question": "Pat Benatar Asked You To \"Hit Me With Your ________\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Beyonc\u00e9", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madonna", 
      "Drake", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Neil Young", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Thal\u00eda", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Janet Jackson", 
      "Moby"
    ], 
    "question": "'Telephone' was a song by which musician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Van Halen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Our Lady Peace", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Shinedown", 
      "Fleetwood Mac", 
      "Cheap Trick"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1972 includes 'Sammy Hagar'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "John Fogerty", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paul Andrews", 
      "Jimmy Toogood", 
      "Bobby Tarbuck"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the lead singer for Creedence Clearwater Revival?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Madonna", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "Drake", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Mika", 
      "Aretha Franklin", 
      "Frank Zappa", 
      "George Michael"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American singer and songwriter released the song 'Material Girl'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Doors", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Styx", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Ratt", 
      "The Cars", 
      "Santana", 
      "Daughtry", 
      "Bowling for Soup"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Robby Krieger'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Weather Report", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Drowning Pool", 
      "Hole", 
      "Type O Negative"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Band Was Formed In The 1970's By Fomer Miles Davis Band Members Joe Zawinul & Wayne Shorter?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Red Hot Chili Peppers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Monkees", 
      "Black Flag", 
      "Journey", 
      "Yellowcard", 
      "Soul Asylum", 
      "Steppenwolf", 
      "W.A.S.P.", 
      "OutKast", 
      "Paramore", 
      "Survivor"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band released the studio album 'Mother's Milk'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Maroon 5", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Styx", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Melvins", 
      "Lady A", 
      "Rancid", 
      "Trivium", 
      "Imagine Dragons", 
      "MGMT", 
      "Thirty Seconds to Mars"
    ], 
    "question": "'Adam Levine' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Austrian", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Czech", 
      "Hungarian", 
      "German"
    ], 
    "question": "What Nationality Was Mozart?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Elton John", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mika", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "John Lennon", 
      "George Michael", 
      "James Blunt", 
      "Ozzy Osbourne", 
      "Phil Collins", 
      "Bonnie Tyler"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Lion King' was a soundtrack album by which musician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Eurythmics", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark", 
      "The Saturdays", 
      "Caravan"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'David A. Stewart'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aerosmith", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "AC/DC", 
      "David Bowie", 
      "Freddie Mercury", 
      "Led Zeppelin"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Suggested \"Lets Get Rocked\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beach Boys", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Swans", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Huey Lewis and the News", 
      "Mudvayne", 
      "De La Soul", 
      "The Four Seasons", 
      "The Everly Brothers", 
      "Rage Against the Machine"
    ], 
    "question": "'Pet Sounds' was a studio album by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Queen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals"
    ], 
    "question": "'John Deacon' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Elvis Costello", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Elton John", 
      "Bob Dylan", 
      "Bono"
    ], 
    "question": "Who In The World Of Music Was Born With The Name \"Declan McManus\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kylie Minogue", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madonna", 
      "Mika", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "John Lennon", 
      "Adele", 
      "Sting", 
      "Peter Gabriel", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Rod Stewart", 
      "James Blunt"
    ], 
    "question": "Which musician released the studio album 'Body Language'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pink Floyd", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wings", 
      "Rudimental", 
      "The Alan Parsons Project", 
      "Basement Jaxx", 
      "Spice Girls", 
      "UB40", 
      "Editors", 
      "Duran Duran", 
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Squeeze"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'David Gilmour'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Status Quo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Saxon", 
      "Pulp", 
      "Rudimental", 
      "Slade", 
      "The Alan Parsons Project", 
      "Basement Jaxx"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Recorded The Albums \"In The Army Now\" And \"Whatever You Want\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Toto", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Styx", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "The Monkees", 
      "Scissor Sisters", 
      "Black Flag", 
      "Journey", 
      "Yellowcard", 
      "Steppenwolf"
    ], 
    "question": "'Africa' was a song by which American rock band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Linkin Park", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alice in Chains", 
      "Hollywood Undead", 
      "System of a Down", 
      "Cameo", 
      "Lady A", 
      "Rancid", 
      "Trivium", 
      "Imagine Dragons", 
      "MGMT", 
      "The Mars Volta"
    ], 
    "question": "'Brad Delson' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Banjo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fiddle", 
      "Ukelele", 
      "Accordion"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The Guitar Like Instrument With A Circular Belly Of Streched Parchment", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Led Zeppelin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Lostprophets", 
      "The Kinks", 
      "King Crimson", 
      "Whitesnake", 
      "Gorillaz", 
      "Kaiser Chiefs", 
      "Jethro Tull", 
      "The Yardbirds", 
      "Venom"
    ], 
    "question": "'Stairway to Heaven' was a song by which English rock band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rammstein", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cascada", 
      "Blue System", 
      "Scorpions", 
      "Running Wild", 
      "B\u00f6hse Onkelz", 
      "Can", 
      "Accept", 
      "Modern Talking", 
      "U.D.O.", 
      "Rage"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1994 includes 'Till Lindemann'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Madonna", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rihanna", 
      "Beyonce", 
      "Lady Gaga"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Female Icon Brought Out A Book Entitled \"Sex\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Radiohead", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Goldfrapp", 
      "Cream", 
      "Girls Aloud", 
      "Bloc Party", 
      "Eurythmics", 
      "The Chemical Brothers", 
      "T. Rex", 
      "The Moody Blues", 
      "The Shadows", 
      "DragonForce"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English rock band released the studio album 'Kid A'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Linkin Park", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alice in Chains", 
      "Hollywood Undead", 
      "System of a Down", 
      "Cameo", 
      "Lady A", 
      "Rancid", 
      "Trivium", 
      "Imagine Dragons", 
      "MGMT", 
      "The Mars Volta"
    ], 
    "question": "'Brad Delson' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "You're The One That I Want", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Islands in the Stream", 
      "I've Got You Babe", 
      "Ain't No Mountain High Enough"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was the Best Selling Single In The UK In The 20th Century By A Duo?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "ABBA", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "In Flames", 
      "HammerFall", 
      "Katatonia", 
      "Meshuggah", 
      "Dark Tranquillity", 
      "The Hives", 
      "Europe", 
      "Vikingarna", 
      "Kent", 
      "Bathory"
    ], 
    "question": "'Waterloo' was an album by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fleetwood Mac", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "W.A.S.P.", 
      "Paramore", 
      "Alice in Chains", 
      "Green Day", 
      "Dio", 
      "Blink-182", 
      "Foo Fighters", 
      "Ramones", 
      "My Chemical Romance", 
      "Dropkick Murphys"
    ], 
    "question": "'Liza Minnelli' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Flight Suits", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bikinis", 
      "Nothing", 
      "Tuxedos"
    ], 
    "question": "What Clothing Are The 2 Figures Wearing On The 1978 Black Sabbath Album Cover \"Never Say Die\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Cure", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Snow Patrol", 
      "Lostprophets", 
      "The Kinks", 
      "King Crimson", 
      "Whitesnake", 
      "Gorillaz", 
      "Kaiser Chiefs", 
      "Jethro Tull"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band released the studio album 'Kiss Me, Kiss Me, Kiss Me'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Black Eyed Peas", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Shinedown", 
      "Fleetwood Mac", 
      "Cheap Trick", 
      "Red Hot Chili Peppers", 
      "Chevelle", 
      "Sweetbox"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1995 includes 'will.i.am'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cher", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cheryl Crowe", 
      "Cheryl (Tweedy/Cole)", 
      "Cheryl Lynn"
    ], 
    "question": "Cherilyn Sarkisian Lapiere Is The Real Name Of Which Singer", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pink Floyd", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wings", 
      "Rudimental", 
      "The Alan Parsons Project", 
      "Basement Jaxx", 
      "Spice Girls", 
      "UB40", 
      "Editors", 
      "Duran Duran", 
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Squeeze"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English rock band released the song 'Comfortably Numb'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Daft Punk", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gong", 
      "Indochine", 
      "Nouvelle Vague", 
      "Air", 
      "Superbus", 
      "Kraftwerk", 
      "Depeche Mode", 
      "R\u00f6yksopp", 
      "Basement Jaxx", 
      "Yellow Magic Orchestra"
    ], 
    "question": "'Thomas Bangalter' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "George Harrison", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "John Lennon", 
      "Paul McCartney", 
      "Ringo Starr"
    ], 
    "question": "Who was the first Beatle to have a solo No 1 hit?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "ABBA", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "In Flames", 
      "HammerFall", 
      "Katatonia", 
      "Meshuggah", 
      "Dark Tranquillity", 
      "The Hives", 
      "Europe", 
      "Vikingarna", 
      "Kent", 
      "Bathory"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band released the song 'Happy New Year'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bee Gees", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Culture Club", 
      "Dire Straits", 
      "Saxon", 
      "Pulp", 
      "The Stone Roses", 
      "Roxy Music", 
      "Stereolab", 
      "Simply Red", 
      "Massive Attack"
    ], 
    "question": "'Robin Gibb' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Billy Joel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "George Michael", 
      "Stevie Wonder", 
      "Cyndi Lauper"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Had A 1984 Hit With The Song \"The Longest Time\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals", 
      "Wire"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English rock band released the song 'Good Night'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Toto", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Styx", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "The Monkees", 
      "Scissor Sisters", 
      "Black Flag", 
      "Journey", 
      "Yellowcard", 
      "Steppenwolf"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1977 includes 'Steve Lukather'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "You're The One That I Want", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Islands in the Stream", 
      "I've Got You Babe", 
      "Ain't No Mountain High Enough"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was the Best Selling Single In The UK In The 20th Century By A Duo?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Led Zeppelin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Lostprophets", 
      "The Kinks", 
      "King Crimson", 
      "Whitesnake", 
      "Gorillaz", 
      "Kaiser Chiefs", 
      "Jethro Tull", 
      "The Yardbirds", 
      "Venom"
    ], 
    "question": "'Black Dog' was a song by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "King Crimson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mogwai", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Sade", 
      "Lloyd Cole and the Commotions", 
      "Primal Scream", 
      "The Pretenders", 
      "Marillion", 
      "Nazareth", 
      "Bastille", 
      "Belle and Sebastian"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Adrian Belew'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bono", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chris Martin", 
      "Paul McCartney", 
      "Phil Collins"
    ], 
    "question": "On the Single \u201c Do They Know It's Christmas \u201d Only One Person Performed On Both The Original And The 20 Year Remake Band Aid 20, Who Was It?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Coldplay", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band released the studio album 'A Head Full of Dreams'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Enigma", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Blue System", 
      "Scorpions", 
      "KMFDM", 
      "Kreator", 
      "Blind Guardian", 
      "Tangerine Dream", 
      "Alphaville", 
      "Gamma Ray", 
      "Scooter", 
      "Boney M."
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Michael Cretu'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Glen Campbell", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bob Dylan", 
      "Bruce Springsteen", 
      "Neil Young"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Singer Started As A Session Guitarist Working With The Likes Of Bobby Darin , Frank Sinatra, Dean Martin & The Beach Boys?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Queen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals"
    ], 
    "question": "Which British rock band (1970-) released the album 'Flash Gordon'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sabaton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Cardigans", 
      "Babymetal", 
      "Scorpions", 
      "Millencolin", 
      "Alcazar", 
      "Ace of Base", 
      "Blind Guardian", 
      "Manowar", 
      "Dark Tranquillity", 
      "Bathory"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'P\u00e4r Sundstr\u00f6m'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "I Just Called To Say I Love You", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "I Wish", 
      "Sir Duke", 
      "Superstitious"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Stevie Wonder Hit Featured In The Movie \u201cThe Woman In Red\u201d?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Within Temptation", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Luv'", 
      "The Cats", 
      "2 Unlimited", 
      "Golden Earring", 
      "Epica", 
      "Yes", 
      "Rhapsody of Fire", 
      "Powerwolf", 
      "Muse", 
      "Paradise Lost"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Dutch metal band released the studio album 'The Heart of Everything'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Blink-182", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Grand Funk Railroad", 
      "Drowning Pool", 
      "Hole", 
      "Type O Negative", 
      "Yeah Yeah Yeahs", 
      "Jimmy Eat World", 
      "Shinedown", 
      "Overkill", 
      "Danzig", 
      "Boyz II Men"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1992 includes 'Travis Barker'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beach Boys", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Huey Lewis and the News", 
      "The Ramones", 
      "Creedence Clearwater Revival"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Group Was Banned From The Official Washington 4th July Celebrations In 1983 Because Secretary Of The Interior Said They Would Attract An Undesirable Element?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rihanna", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Drake", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Ricky Martin", 
      "Madonna", 
      "will.i.am", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "Bruno Mars", 
      "Ne-Yo", 
      "George Michael", 
      "Michael Jackson"
    ], 
    "question": "Which musician released the studio album 'Loud'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Guns N' Roses", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Iced Earth", 
      "Exodus", 
      "Goo Goo Dolls", 
      "Crosby, Stills & Nash", 
      "Daryl Hall & John Oates", 
      "Blackmore's Night"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Buckethead'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dire Straits", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "The Moody Blues", 
      "The Shadows", 
      "Porcupine Tree", 
      "Procol Harum", 
      "The Who", 
      "Queen", 
      "Fleetwood Mac", 
      "Creedence Clearwater Revival"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Recorded The Album \"Love Over Gold\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Britney Spears", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madonna", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Drake", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Bruce Springsteen", 
      "Aretha Franklin", 
      "Frank Zappa", 
      "Ricky Martin", 
      "Janet Jackson"
    ], 
    "question": "Which musician released the song 'Perfume'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Queen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals"
    ], 
    "question": "'John Deacon' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Common People", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Don't Look Back In Anger", 
      "Coffee & TV", 
      "Smells Like Teen Spirit"
    ], 
    "question": "Which 90's Song Opens With The Line \"She Came From Greece She Had A Thirst For Knowledge\"? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals", 
      "Wire"
    ], 
    "question": "'1962\u20131966' was a compilation album by which English rock band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Led Zeppelin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Lostprophets", 
      "The Kinks", 
      "King Crimson", 
      "Whitesnake", 
      "Gorillaz", 
      "Kaiser Chiefs", 
      "Jethro Tull", 
      "The Yardbirds", 
      "Venom"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1968 includes 'Robert Plant'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Cardigans", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Coldplay", 
      "Ace of Base", 
      "Westlife"
    ], 
    "question": "Whose 1996 Debut Album Was Entitled \"First Band On The Moon\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Queen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals"
    ], 
    "question": "'Flash' was a song by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Destiny's Child", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Shinedown", 
      "Fleetwood Mac", 
      "Cheap Trick", 
      "Red Hot Chili Peppers", 
      "Chevelle", 
      "Sweetbox"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1990 includes 'Beyonc\u00e9'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Don't You Want Me Baby", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Never Tear Us Apart", 
      "What is Love", 
      "Slave To The Rhythm"
    ], 
    "question": "What Song Features The Lyric \"I Was Working As A Waitress In A Cocktail Bar\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nirvana", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Counting Crows", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "The Mothers of Invention", 
      "L.A. Guns", 
      "Nitty Gritty Dirt Band", 
      "Animal Collective", 
      "Mastodon", 
      "Poco", 
      "Ha*Ash"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American rock band released the song 'Sliver'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Toto", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Styx", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "The Monkees", 
      "Scissor Sisters", 
      "Black Flag", 
      "Journey", 
      "Yellowcard", 
      "Steppenwolf"
    ], 
    "question": "'Steve Lukather' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cars", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Trains", 
      "Planes", 
      "Boats"
    ], 
    "question": "Gary Numan Sang An 80's Hit About Which Mode Of Transport?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Who", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Travis", 
      "Spandau Ballet", 
      "All Saints", 
      "Skunk Anansie", 
      "10cc", 
      "Arctic Monkeys", 
      "Joy Division", 
      "Franz Ferdinand", 
      "Magnum"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band released the studio album 'Who's Next'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Guns N' Roses", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Iced Earth", 
      "Exodus", 
      "Goo Goo Dolls", 
      "Crosby, Stills & Nash", 
      "Daryl Hall & John Oates", 
      "Blackmore's Night"
    ], 
    "question": "'Izzy Stradlin' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rock Around The Clock", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Johnny B Goode", 
      "Candy Girl", 
      "Old Time Rock and Roll"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Bill Haley song became the U.K.'s first Rock and Roll number one?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dream Theater", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jars of Clay", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Shinedown", 
      "Fleetwood Mac", 
      "Cheap Trick", 
      "Red Hot Chili Peppers", 
      "Chevelle", 
      "Crosby, Stills & Nash"
    ], 
    "question": "'Images and Words' was a studio album by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Take That", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Talk Talk", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Bring Me the Horizon", 
      "My Dying Bride", 
      "Wet Wet Wet", 
      "Culture Club", 
      "Dire Straits", 
      "Saxon", 
      "Pulp", 
      "Rudimental"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1990 includes 'Gary Barlow'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Barbra Streisand", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madonna", 
      "Hilary Duff", 
      "Aretha Franklin"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American singer starred in the film 'Hello, Dolly!'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Radiohead", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Goldfrapp", 
      "Cream", 
      "Girls Aloud", 
      "Bloc Party", 
      "Eurythmics", 
      "The Chemical Brothers", 
      "T. Rex", 
      "The Moody Blues", 
      "The Shadows", 
      "DragonForce"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English rock band released the album 'In Rainbows'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Iron Maiden", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Squeeze", 
      "Talk Talk", 
      "Goldfrapp", 
      "Camel", 
      "Wings", 
      "Mogwai", 
      "Sade", 
      "Lloyd Cole and the Commotions"
    ], 
    "question": "'Adrian Smith' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Prince", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Celine Dion", 
      "Barry Gibb", 
      "Elvis Presley"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Wrote The Songs \"Manic Monday\" , \"Nothing Compares To You\" And \"I Feel For You\"? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Elton John", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mika", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "John Lennon", 
      "George Michael", 
      "James Blunt", 
      "Ozzy Osbourne", 
      "Phil Collins", 
      "Bonnie Tyler"
    ], 
    "question": "'Your Song' was a song by which English rock singer-songwriter, composer and pianist?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Roxette", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arch Enemy", 
      "Sabaton", 
      "Europe", 
      "HammerFall", 
      "The Cardigans", 
      "Opeth", 
      "Alcazar", 
      "Vikingarna", 
      "Kent", 
      "Amon Amarth"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Marie Fredriksson'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Devo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Switchfoot", 
      "Genesis", 
      "The Hollies", 
      "The Zombies"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The Band That Had Hits With \"Freedom Of Choice\" \"Beatiful World\" & \"Working In A Coalmine\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Linkin Park", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alice in Chains", 
      "Hollywood Undead", 
      "System of a Down", 
      "Cameo", 
      "Lady A", 
      "Rancid", 
      "Trivium", 
      "Imagine Dragons", 
      "MGMT", 
      "The Mars Volta"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American rock band released the studio album 'Meteora'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Velvet Underground", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alice in Chains", 
      "Marilyn Manson", 
      "Fall Out Boy", 
      "Simon & Garfunkel", 
      "The Mars Volta", 
      "Deftones", 
      "Good Charlotte", 
      "Cannibal Corpse", 
      "Garbage", 
      "Insane Clown Posse"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1965 includes 'Maureen Tucker'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Paranoid", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Psycho", 
      "Crazy", 
      "Insane"
    ], 
    "question": "Name Black Sabbath's debut hit?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lady Gaga", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Drake", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Neil Young", 
      "Aretha Franklin", 
      "Frank Zappa", 
      "Christina Aguilera", 
      "Britney Spears"
    ], 
    "question": "'Paparazzi' was a song by which American singer, songwriter, and actress?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "AC/DC", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pendulum", 
      "INXS", 
      "Savage Garden", 
      "Powderfinger", 
      "The Easybeats", 
      "Air Supply", 
      "The Living End", 
      "Silverchair", 
      "Dead Can Dance", 
      "Tame Impala"
    ], 
    "question": "'Angus Young' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ace Of Base", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Modern Talking", 
      "The Cardigans", 
      "Every Little Thing", 
      "Dream", 
      "Blue System", 
      "Matia Bazar"
    ], 
    "question": "Jenny & Lyn Beggren Are Singers With Which 90's Group", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Beyonc\u00e9", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madonna", 
      "Drake", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Neil Young", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Thal\u00eda", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Janet Jackson", 
      "Moby"
    ], 
    "question": "'Listen' was a song by which musician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Judas Priest", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arctic Monkeys", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Bring Me the Horizon", 
      "My Dying Bride", 
      "Wet Wet Wet", 
      "Culture Club", 
      "Dire Straits", 
      "Saxon", 
      "Pulp", 
      "Rudimental"
    ], 
    "question": "'Glenn Tipton' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Stranglers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Cheap Trick", 
      "Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark", 
      "Camel", 
      "Wings"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Mod Revival Band Did The Style Councils Mick Talbot Play The Keyboard? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Michael Jackson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Neil Young", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Drake", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Ludacris", 
      "Janet Jackson", 
      "Beck"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American singer, songwriter and dancer released the song 'Leave Me Alone'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Gorillaz", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Magnum", 
      "Spandau Ballet", 
      "All Saints", 
      "Skunk Anansie", 
      "10cc", 
      "Arctic Monkeys", 
      "Joy Division", 
      "Franz Ferdinand", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Supertramp"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1998 includes 'Damon Albarn'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "2", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1/2", 
      "4", 
      "8"
    ], 
    "question": "How Many Crotchets Do You Get In A Minim?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Depeche Mode", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Dead or Alive", 
      "Radiohead", 
      "Iron Maiden", 
      "Oasis", 
      "Echo & the Bunnymen", 
      "The Darkness", 
      "Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark", 
      "Funeral for a Friend", 
      "Texas"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band released the album 'Black Celebration'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Guns N' Roses", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Iced Earth", 
      "Exodus", 
      "Goo Goo Dolls", 
      "Crosby, Stills & Nash", 
      "Daryl Hall & John Oates", 
      "Blackmore's Night"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1985 includes 'Izzy Stradlin'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Roxette", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arch Enemy", 
      "Sabaton", 
      "Europe", 
      "HammerFall", 
      "The Cardigans", 
      "Opeth"
    ], 
    "question": "Whose Greatest Hits Album Was Entitled \"Don't Bore Us With The Chorus\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lady Gaga", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Drake", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Neil Young", 
      "Aretha Franklin", 
      "Frank Zappa", 
      "Christina Aguilera", 
      "Britney Spears"
    ], 
    "question": "Which musician released the song 'You and I'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals", 
      "Wire"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1960 includes 'Ringo Starr'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Robert Bell", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mark DuPont", 
      "Lawrence Jones", 
      "Gary Helman"
    ], 
    "question": "What was the real name of Kool, of Kool and the Gang fame?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rihanna", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Drake", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Ricky Martin", 
      "Madonna", 
      "will.i.am", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "Bruno Mars", 
      "Ne-Yo", 
      "George Michael", 
      "Michael Jackson"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Barbadian singer, songwriter, and businesswoman released the studio album 'Loud'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Who", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Travis", 
      "Spandau Ballet", 
      "All Saints", 
      "Skunk Anansie", 
      "10cc", 
      "Arctic Monkeys", 
      "Joy Division", 
      "Franz Ferdinand", 
      "Magnum"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1964 includes 'Pete Townshend'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aswad", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Abrah", 
      "Salar", 
      "Jawab"
    ], 
    "question": "Which pop group took their name from the Arabic word for black?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "C\u00e9line Dion", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mina", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Ricky Martin", 
      "Mika", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Drake", 
      "Phil Collins", 
      "Bruno Mars"
    ], 
    "question": "'My Heart Will Go On' was a song by which Canadian singer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Creedence Clearwater Revival", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Crosby, Stills & Nash", 
      "Daryl Hall & John Oates", 
      "Blackmore's Night", 
      "OK Go", 
      "Sevendust", 
      "Primus"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'John Fogerty'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Blondie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Prince and the Revolution", 
      "Me First and the Gimme Gimmes", 
      "The Flaming Lips", 
      "Poison", 
      "Michael Jackson"
    ], 
    "question": "Whose Albums Included Plastic Letters & Parallel Lines", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Bowie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Mika", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "Robbie Williams", 
      "Ed Sheeran", 
      "Kate Bush", 
      "Joe Cocker", 
      "Mark Knopfler", 
      "John Lennon"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Rise and Fall of Ziggy Stardust and the Spiders from Mars' was an album by which musician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "ABBA", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "In Flames", 
      "HammerFall", 
      "Katatonia", 
      "Meshuggah", 
      "Dark Tranquillity", 
      "The Hives", 
      "Europe", 
      "Vikingarna", 
      "Kent", 
      "Bathory"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Anni-Frid Lyngstad'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Liverpool", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Manchester", 
      "Newcastle", 
      "Leeds"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Northern UK English city Did The Beatles Come From?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Elton John", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mika", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "John Lennon", 
      "George Michael", 
      "James Blunt", 
      "Ozzy Osbourne", 
      "Phil Collins", 
      "Bonnie Tyler"
    ], 
    "question": "Which musician performed the threnody 'Candle in the Wind'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Linkin Park", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alice in Chains", 
      "Hollywood Undead", 
      "System of a Down", 
      "Cameo", 
      "Lady A", 
      "Rancid", 
      "Trivium", 
      "Imagine Dragons", 
      "MGMT", 
      "The Mars Volta"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1996 includes 'Chester Bennington'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Right Said Fred", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Our Lady Peace", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Tube", 
      "ClariS", 
      "Field of View"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Had A Hit In 1994 With \"Wonderman\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Jimi Hendrix Experience", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Poison", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Goo Goo Dolls", 
      "Crosby, Stills & Nash", 
      "Daryl Hall & John Oates", 
      "Blackmore's Night", 
      "OK Go", 
      "Sevendust"
    ], 
    "question": "'Are You Experienced' was an album by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sonic Youth", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Fall Out Boy", 
      "Marilyn Manson", 
      "M\u00f6tley Cr\u00fce", 
      "Jefferson Airplane", 
      "LMFAO", 
      "Static-X", 
      "P.O.D."
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Richard Edson'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "You're The One That I Want", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Islands in the Stream", 
      "I've Got You Babe", 
      "Ain't No Mountain High Enough"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was the Best Selling Single In The UK In The 20th Century By A Duo?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Madonna", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "Drake", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Mika", 
      "Aretha Franklin", 
      "Frank Zappa", 
      "George Michael"
    ], 
    "question": "Which musician released the studio album 'Rebel Heart'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "One Direction", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark", 
      "Blur", 
      "Anathema", 
      "Cradle of Filth", 
      "The Sweet", 
      "The Verve", 
      "Hurts", 
      "Bring Me the Horizon", 
      "My Dying Bride"
    ], 
    "question": "'Louis Tomlinson' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Wet Wet Wet", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Feeder", 
      "Wham!", 
      "Culture Club"
    ], 
    "question": "Who had 90's hits with 'Julia Says' & 'If I Never See You Again'? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lady Gaga", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Drake", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Neil Young", 
      "Aretha Franklin", 
      "Frank Zappa", 
      "Christina Aguilera", 
      "Britney Spears"
    ], 
    "question": "'Hair' was a song by which musician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Girls' Generation", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Big Bang", 
      "BTS", 
      "Apink", 
      "F.T. Island", 
      "CNBLUE", 
      "EXO", 
      "T-ara", 
      "TVXQ", 
      "GFriend", 
      "(G)I-dle"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 2007 includes 'Taeyeon'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Joni Mitchell", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Leonard Cohen", 
      "Elton John", 
      "Tom Waits"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Released The 70's Album Entitled \"Blue\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Depeche Mode", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Dead or Alive", 
      "Radiohead", 
      "Iron Maiden", 
      "Oasis", 
      "Echo & the Bunnymen", 
      "The Darkness", 
      "Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark", 
      "Funeral for a Friend", 
      "Texas"
    ], 
    "question": "'Ultra' was a studio album by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kiss", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Swans", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Mudvayne", 
      "De La Soul", 
      "The Four Seasons", 
      "The Everly Brothers", 
      "Rage Against the Machine", 
      "Switchfoot"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Paul Stanley'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Blondie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Prince and the Revolution", 
      "Me First and the Gimme Gimmes", 
      "The Flaming Lips", 
      "Poison", 
      "Michael Jackson"
    ], 
    "question": "Whose Albums Included Plastic Letters & Parallel Lines", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Muse", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tears for Fears", 
      "Bullet For My Valentine", 
      "Enter Shikari", 
      "Kasabian", 
      "Emerson, Lake & Palmer", 
      "The Fall", 
      "Erasure", 
      "Placebo", 
      "The Cure", 
      "Keane"
    ], 
    "question": "'New Born' was a song by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Talking Heads", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Steve Miller Band", 
      "Rascal Flatts", 
      "Pennywise", 
      "Cake", 
      "Hanson", 
      "The Chainsmokers"
    ], 
    "question": "'Jerry Harrison' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Relax", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Let's Get It On", 
      "Sexual Healing", 
      "Fat Bottomed Girls "
    ], 
    "question": "Which 1983 Shot To The Top Of The UK Charts After Mike Reid Refused To Play It On His Radio Show Due To Its Sexual Content? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pink Floyd", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wings", 
      "Rudimental", 
      "The Alan Parsons Project", 
      "Basement Jaxx", 
      "Spice Girls", 
      "UB40", 
      "Editors", 
      "Duran Duran", 
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Squeeze"
    ], 
    "question": "'Us and Them' was a song by which English rock band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The White Stripes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Good Charlotte", 
      "Cannibal Corpse", 
      "Garbage", 
      "Fall Out Boy", 
      "Marilyn Manson", 
      "M\u00f6tley Cr\u00fce", 
      "Jefferson Airplane"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1997 includes 'Jack White'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aswad", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Abrah", 
      "Salar", 
      "Jawab"
    ], 
    "question": "Which pop group took their name from the Arabic word for black?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Madonna", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "Drake", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Mika", 
      "Aretha Franklin", 
      "Frank Zappa", 
      "George Michael"
    ], 
    "question": "'Die Another Day' was a song by which musician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Who", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Travis", 
      "Spandau Ballet", 
      "All Saints", 
      "Skunk Anansie", 
      "10cc", 
      "Arctic Monkeys", 
      "Joy Division", 
      "Franz Ferdinand", 
      "Magnum"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1964 includes 'Roger Daltrey'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Beethoven", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bach", 
      "Mozart", 
      "Schubert"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Composed The Pastoral Symphony?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nightwish", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Haloo Helsinki!", 
      "Hanoi Rocks", 
      "Children of Bodom", 
      "Sonata Arctica", 
      "Rhapsody of Fire", 
      "Stratovarius", 
      "Lordi", 
      "HIM", 
      "Amorphis", 
      "Apocalyptica"
    ], 
    "question": "'Once' was an album by which Finnish symphonic metal band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Supremes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Live", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Overkill", 
      "Danzig", 
      "Boyz II Men", 
      "Four Tops", 
      "Huey Lewis and the News", 
      "Mudvayne"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Diana Ross'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Britney Spears", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madonna", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Drake", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Bruce Springsteen", 
      "Aretha Franklin", 
      "Frank Zappa", 
      "Ricky Martin", 
      "Janet Jackson"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American singer released the song 'Everytime'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Rolling Stones", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "McFly", 
      "Delirious?", 
      "Depeche Mode", 
      "All Saints", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "One Direction", 
      "Fairport Convention", 
      "Thompson Twins", 
      "Tears for Fears", 
      "Il Divo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Honky Tonk Women' was a song by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Judas Priest", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arctic Monkeys", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Bring Me the Horizon", 
      "My Dying Bride", 
      "Wet Wet Wet", 
      "Culture Club", 
      "Dire Straits", 
      "Saxon", 
      "Pulp", 
      "Rudimental"
    ], 
    "question": "'K. K. Downing' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Gideon's Bible", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Loaded Gun", 
      "What He'd Lost", 
      "His Doom"
    ], 
    "question": "According To The Beatles What did Rocky Racoon find in his room?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kate Bush", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "David Bowie", 
      "John Lennon", 
      "George Michael", 
      "James Blunt", 
      "Ozzy Osbourne", 
      "Phil Collins", 
      "Bonnie Tyler", 
      "Ellie Goulding", 
      "Donovan", 
      "Ed Sheeran"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Red Shoes' was a studio album by which musician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "OneRepublic", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Collective Soul", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Black Flag", 
      "Journey", 
      "Yellowcard", 
      "Steppenwolf", 
      "W.A.S.P.", 
      "OutKast", 
      "Paramore"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1996 includes 'Ryan Tedder'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Britney Spears", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madonna", 
      "Janet Jackson", 
      "Christina Aguilera"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American singer released the song 'Stronger'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Led Zeppelin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Lostprophets", 
      "The Kinks", 
      "King Crimson", 
      "Whitesnake", 
      "Gorillaz", 
      "Kaiser Chiefs", 
      "Jethro Tull", 
      "The Yardbirds", 
      "Venom"
    ], 
    "question": "'BBC Sessions' was a live album by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oasis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Goldfrapp", 
      "Kaiser Chiefs", 
      "Jethro Tull", 
      "The Yardbirds", 
      "Venom", 
      "Sugababes", 
      "Noel Gallagher's High Flying Birds", 
      "Mot\u00f6rhead", 
      "Jamiroquai", 
      "Cream"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1991 includes 'Noel Gallagher'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "I Heard It Through The Grapevine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "What's Going On?", 
      "Mercy Mercy Me", 
      "Sexual Healing"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was Marvin Gaye's Only UK No.1?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lady Gaga", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Drake", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Neil Young", 
      "Aretha Franklin", 
      "Frank Zappa", 
      "Christina Aguilera", 
      "Britney Spears"
    ], 
    "question": "'LoveGame' was a song by which musician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Linkin Park", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alice in Chains", 
      "Hollywood Undead", 
      "System of a Down", 
      "Cameo", 
      "Lady A", 
      "Rancid", 
      "Trivium", 
      "Imagine Dragons", 
      "MGMT", 
      "The Mars Volta"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Joseph Hahn'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Devo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Switchfoot", 
      "Genesis", 
      "The Hollies", 
      "The Zombies"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The Band That Had Hits With \"Freedom Of Choice\" \"Beatiful World\" & \"Working In A Coalmine\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Rolling Stones", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "McFly", 
      "Delirious?", 
      "Depeche Mode", 
      "All Saints", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "One Direction", 
      "Fairport Convention", 
      "Thompson Twins", 
      "Tears for Fears", 
      "Il Divo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Brown Sugar' was a song by which English rock band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beach Boys", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Swans", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Huey Lewis and the News", 
      "Mudvayne", 
      "De La Soul", 
      "The Four Seasons", 
      "The Everly Brothers", 
      "Rage Against the Machine"
    ], 
    "question": "'Dennis Wilson' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sheena Easton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Shirley Bassey", 
      "Adele", 
      "The White Stripes"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Sang The James Bond Theme \"For Your Eyes Only\"? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Beyonc\u00e9", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madonna", 
      "Drake", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Neil Young", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Thal\u00eda", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Janet Jackson", 
      "Moby"
    ], 
    "question": "Which musician released the song 'D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Linkin Park", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alice in Chains", 
      "Hollywood Undead", 
      "System of a Down", 
      "Cameo", 
      "Lady A", 
      "Rancid", 
      "Trivium", 
      "Imagine Dragons", 
      "MGMT", 
      "The Mars Volta"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1996 includes 'Joseph Hahn'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Elvis Costello", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Elton John", 
      "Bob Dylan", 
      "Bono"
    ], 
    "question": "Who In The World Of Music Was Born With The Name \"Declan McManus\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Michael Jackson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Neil Young", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Drake", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Ludacris", 
      "Janet Jackson", 
      "Beck"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American singer, songwriter and dancer released the album 'Bad'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Depeche Mode", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Dead or Alive", 
      "Radiohead", 
      "Iron Maiden", 
      "Oasis", 
      "Echo & the Bunnymen", 
      "The Darkness", 
      "Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark", 
      "Funeral for a Friend", 
      "Texas"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1980 includes 'Dave Gahan'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Unchained Melody", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Careless Whisper", 
      "Let's Get It On", 
      "The Lady In Red"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Song Ends With The Line \"God Speed Your Love To Me\"? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals", 
      "Wire"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band released the studio album 'Anthology 3'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Led Zeppelin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Lostprophets", 
      "The Kinks", 
      "King Crimson", 
      "Whitesnake", 
      "Gorillaz", 
      "Kaiser Chiefs", 
      "Jethro Tull", 
      "The Yardbirds", 
      "Venom"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1968 includes 'John Bonham'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ace Of Base", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Modern Talking", 
      "The Cardigans", 
      "Every Little Thing", 
      "Dream", 
      "Blue System", 
      "Matia Bazar"
    ], 
    "question": "Jenny & Lyn Beggren Are Singers With Which 90's Group", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pink Floyd", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wings", 
      "Rudimental", 
      "The Alan Parsons Project", 
      "Basement Jaxx", 
      "Spice Girls", 
      "UB40", 
      "Editors", 
      "Duran Duran", 
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Squeeze"
    ], 
    "question": "'A Nice Pair' was a compilation album by which English rock band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dire Straits", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "The Moody Blues", 
      "The Shadows", 
      "DragonForce", 
      "Porcupine Tree", 
      "Procol Harum", 
      "New Order", 
      "Manic Street Preachers", 
      "Florence + the Machine", 
      "Electric Light Orchestra"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Eric Clapton'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Led Zeppelin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pink Floyd", 
      "Rolling Stones", 
      "Queen"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Physical Graffiti?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Iron Maiden", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Squeeze", 
      "Talk Talk", 
      "Goldfrapp", 
      "Camel", 
      "Wings", 
      "Mogwai", 
      "Sade", 
      "Lloyd Cole and the Commotions"
    ], 
    "question": "'Seventh Son of a Seventh Son' was an album by which English heavy metal band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rammstein", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cascada", 
      "Blue System", 
      "Scorpions", 
      "Running Wild", 
      "B\u00f6hse Onkelz", 
      "Can", 
      "Accept", 
      "Modern Talking", 
      "U.D.O.", 
      "Rage"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1994 includes 'Till Lindemann'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Manfred Mann", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Pupert Holmes"
    ], 
    "question": "Which 60's Star Was Born In Johannesburg And Christened Michael Lubowitz?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Madonna", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "Drake", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Mika", 
      "Aretha Franklin", 
      "Frank Zappa", 
      "George Michael"
    ], 
    "question": "'Vogue' was a song by which musician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Whitesnake", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Blur", 
      "Bullet For My Valentine", 
      "Erasure", 
      "Black Sabbath", 
      "Placebo", 
      "The Cure", 
      "Depeche Mode", 
      "Keane", 
      "Texas", 
      "The Jam"
    ], 
    "question": "'David Coverdale' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Wings", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "The Chemical Brothers", 
      "T. Rex", 
      "The Moody Blues", 
      "The Shadows", 
      "DragonForce", 
      "Porcupine Tree", 
      "Procol Harum", 
      "New Order"
    ], 
    "question": "'Band on the Run' was an album by which British\u2013American rock band led by Paul McCartney?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Destiny's Child", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Shinedown", 
      "Fleetwood Mac", 
      "Cheap Trick", 
      "Red Hot Chili Peppers", 
      "Chevelle", 
      "Sweetbox"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1990 includes 'Beyonc\u00e9'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Eva Cassidy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Norah Jones", 
      "Dido", 
      "Karen Carpenter"
    ], 
    "question": "Whose Album 'Songbird' Became A Posthumous Hit In 2001?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kylie Minogue", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madonna", 
      "Mika", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "John Lennon", 
      "Adele", 
      "Sting", 
      "Peter Gabriel", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Rod Stewart", 
      "James Blunt"
    ], 
    "question": "Which musician released the studio album 'X'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "ABBA", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "In Flames", 
      "HammerFall", 
      "Katatonia", 
      "Meshuggah", 
      "Dark Tranquillity", 
      "The Hives", 
      "Europe", 
      "Vikingarna", 
      "Kent", 
      "Bathory"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Benny Andersson'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Barbara Streisand", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dolly Parton", 
      "Grace Jones", 
      "Cher"
    ], 
    "question": "Which US Singer Duetted With Donna Summer On The US Number One 'No More Tears'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Bowie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Mika", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "Robbie Williams", 
      "Ed Sheeran", 
      "Kate Bush", 
      "Joe Cocker", 
      "Mark Knopfler", 
      "John Lennon"
    ], 
    "question": "Which musician released the album 'The Man Who Sold the World'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Guns N' Roses", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Iced Earth", 
      "Exodus", 
      "Goo Goo Dolls", 
      "Crosby, Stills & Nash", 
      "Daryl Hall & John Oates", 
      "Blackmore's Night"
    ], 
    "question": "'Buckethead' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aerosmith", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "The Everly Brothers", 
      "Rage Against the Machine", 
      "AC/DC", 
      "Guns n Roses", 
      "The Hives"
    ], 
    "question": "Steven Tyler Is Lead Vocalist With Which Rock Band", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Queensr\u00ffche", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Shinedown", 
      "Fleetwood Mac", 
      "Cheap Trick", 
      "Red Hot Chili Peppers", 
      "Chevelle", 
      "Korn"
    ], 
    "question": "'Operation: Mindcrime' was a concept album by which American band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Simon & Garfunkel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "REO Speedwagon", 
      "Lifehouse", 
      "The Temptations", 
      "The Used", 
      "Kool & The Gang", 
      "New Found Glory"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Art Garfunkel'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sticky Fingers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brown Sugar", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Let It Bleed"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Album Cover Did Andy Warhol Design For The Rolling Stones?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals", 
      "Wire"
    ], 
    "question": "'Let It Be\u2026 Naked' was a remix album by which English rock band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Black Eyed Peas", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Shinedown", 
      "Fleetwood Mac", 
      "Cheap Trick", 
      "Red Hot Chili Peppers", 
      "Chevelle", 
      "Sweetbox"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1995 includes 'Fergie'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sheena Easton", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Shirley Bassey", 
      "Adele", 
      "The White Stripes"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Sang The James Bond Theme \"For Your Eyes Only\"? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mariah Carey", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Drake", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Ludacris", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Frank Zappa", 
      "Ricky Martin", 
      "Janet Jackson"
    ], 
    "question": "Which musician performed the musical composition 'Santa Claus Is Coming to Town'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Cranberries", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Corrs", 
      "Boyzone", 
      "Thin Lizzy", 
      "The Pogues", 
      "The Script", 
      "Clannad", 
      "Celtic Woman", 
      "Westlife", 
      "The Dubliners", 
      "U2"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1989 includes 'Dolores O'Riordan'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rednex", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Cardigans", 
      "Alcazar", 
      "Ace of Base"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Had A One Hit Wonder With \"Cotton Eye Joe\" In 1994\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Slayer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Shinedown", 
      "Fleetwood Mac", 
      "Cheap Trick", 
      "Red Hot Chili Peppers", 
      "Chevelle", 
      "Sweetbox"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Big Four: Live from Sofia, Bulgaria' was a concert film by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Linkin Park", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alice in Chains", 
      "Hollywood Undead", 
      "System of a Down", 
      "Cameo", 
      "Lady A", 
      "Rancid", 
      "Trivium", 
      "Imagine Dragons", 
      "MGMT", 
      "The Mars Volta"
    ], 
    "question": "'Dave Farrell' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Devo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Switchfoot", 
      "Genesis", 
      "The Hollies", 
      "The Zombies"
    ], 
    "question": "Name The Band That Had Hits With \"Freedom Of Choice\" \"Beatiful World\" & \"Working In A Coalmine\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Elton John", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mika", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "John Lennon", 
      "George Michael", 
      "James Blunt", 
      "Ozzy Osbourne", 
      "Phil Collins", 
      "Bonnie Tyler"
    ], 
    "question": "'Caribou' was a studio album by which musician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bee Gees", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Culture Club", 
      "Dire Straits", 
      "Saxon", 
      "Pulp", 
      "The Stone Roses", 
      "Roxy Music", 
      "Stereolab", 
      "Simply Red", 
      "Massive Attack"
    ], 
    "question": "'Barry Gibb' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Igor Stravinsky", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gustav Holst", 
      "Franz Schubert", 
      "Joseph Haydn"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Wrote \"The Firebird Suite\" & \"The Ebony Concerto\"? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals", 
      "Wire"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English rock band released the song 'Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Judas Priest", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arctic Monkeys", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Bring Me the Horizon", 
      "My Dying Bride", 
      "Wet Wet Wet", 
      "Culture Club", 
      "Dire Straits", 
      "Saxon", 
      "Pulp", 
      "Rudimental"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1968 includes 'Rob Halford'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steve Harley", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bruce Davidson", 
      "Phil Collins", 
      "Jack Mitchell"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Was Was The Lead Singer With Cockney Rebel?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals", 
      "Wire"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band released the song 'Lady Madonna'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beach Boys", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Swans", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Huey Lewis and the News", 
      "Mudvayne", 
      "De La Soul", 
      "The Four Seasons", 
      "The Everly Brothers", 
      "Rage Against the Machine"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1961 includes 'Brian Wilson'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aswad", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Abrah", 
      "Salar", 
      "Jawab"
    ], 
    "question": "Which pop group took their name from the Arabic word for black?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pink Floyd", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wings", 
      "Rudimental", 
      "The Alan Parsons Project", 
      "Basement Jaxx", 
      "Spice Girls", 
      "UB40", 
      "Editors", 
      "Duran Duran", 
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Squeeze"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Final Cut' was a studio album by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Linkin Park", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alice in Chains", 
      "Hollywood Undead", 
      "System of a Down", 
      "Cameo", 
      "Lady A", 
      "Rancid", 
      "Trivium", 
      "Imagine Dragons", 
      "MGMT", 
      "The Mars Volta"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Brad Delson'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Freeway Of Love", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Freedom Freeway", 
      "Freeway Five", 
      "The Respect Freeway"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Freeway Did \"Aretha Franklin\" Sing About?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Iron Maiden", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Squeeze", 
      "Talk Talk", 
      "Goldfrapp", 
      "Camel", 
      "Wings", 
      "Mogwai", 
      "Sade", 
      "Lloyd Cole and the Commotions"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English heavy metal band released the song 'Aces High'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark", 
      "Nazareth", 
      "Bastille", 
      "Belle and Sebastian", 
      "Herman's Hermits", 
      "The Prodigy", 
      "Bananarama", 
      "Asia", 
      "Soft Machine", 
      "The Human League"
    ], 
    "question": "'Jon Anderson' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oasis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Goldfrapp", 
      "Kaiser Chiefs", 
      "Jethro Tull", 
      "The Yardbirds", 
      "Venom", 
      "Sugababes"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Had A Hit In 1996 With \"Don't Look Back In Anger\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Beyonc\u00e9", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madonna", 
      "Drake", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Neil Young", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Thal\u00eda", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Janet Jackson", 
      "Moby"
    ], 
    "question": "'D\u00e9j\u00e0 Vu' was a song by which American singer, actress and record producer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Arctic Monkeys", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Supertramp", 
      "Yes", 
      "Snow Patrol", 
      "Lostprophets", 
      "The Kinks", 
      "King Crimson", 
      "Whitesnake", 
      "Gorillaz", 
      "Kaiser Chiefs", 
      "Jethro Tull"
    ], 
    "question": "'Alex Turner' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Steve Winwood", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mike Oldfield", 
      "Phil Collins", 
      "Rick Astley"
    ], 
    "question": "\"Higher Love\" Was A Hit For Which UK Artist? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bee Gees", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Culture Club", 
      "Dire Straits", 
      "Saxon", 
      "Pulp", 
      "The Stone Roses", 
      "Roxy Music", 
      "Stereolab", 
      "Simply Red", 
      "Massive Attack"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band released the song 'To Love Somebody'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Spice Girls", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Editors", 
      "Cradle of Filth", 
      "The Sweet", 
      "The Verve", 
      "Hurts", 
      "Bring Me the Horizon", 
      "My Dying Bride", 
      "Wet Wet Wet", 
      "Culture Club", 
      "Dire Straits"
    ], 
    "question": "'Melanie C' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Stevie Wonder", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Stevie Nicks", 
      "Stevie Ray Vaughan", 
      "Stevie Winwood"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Released The 70's Album Entitled \"Innervisions\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Led Zeppelin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Lostprophets", 
      "The Kinks", 
      "King Crimson", 
      "Whitesnake", 
      "Gorillaz", 
      "Kaiser Chiefs", 
      "Jethro Tull", 
      "The Yardbirds", 
      "Venom"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English rock band released the album 'Physical Graffiti'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Placebo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Magnum", 
      "Kaiser Chiefs", 
      "Jethro Tull", 
      "The Yardbirds", 
      "Venom", 
      "Sugababes", 
      "Noel Gallagher's High Flying Birds", 
      "Mot\u00f6rhead", 
      "Jamiroquai", 
      "Cream"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1994 includes 'Brian Molko'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Barbara Streisand", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dolly Parton", 
      "Grace Jones", 
      "Cher"
    ], 
    "question": "Which US Singer Duetted With Donna Summer On The US Number One 'No More Tears'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bob Dylan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Neil Young", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Alicia Keys", 
      "Hilary Duff", 
      "Bruce Springsteen", 
      "Aretha Franklin", 
      "Frank Zappa", 
      "Janet Jackson", 
      "Moby"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American recording artist, singer-songwriter, musician, author, artist and Nobel Laureate in 2016 released the song 'Like a Rolling Stone'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "King Crimson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mogwai", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Sade", 
      "Lloyd Cole and the Commotions", 
      "Primal Scream", 
      "The Pretenders", 
      "Marillion", 
      "Nazareth", 
      "Bastille", 
      "Belle and Sebastian"
    ], 
    "question": "'Adrian Belew' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Stranglers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Cheap Trick", 
      "Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark", 
      "Camel", 
      "Wings"
    ], 
    "question": "With Which Mod Revival Band Did The Style Councils Mick Talbot Play The Keyboard? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Depeche Mode", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Dead or Alive", 
      "Radiohead", 
      "Iron Maiden", 
      "Oasis", 
      "Echo & the Bunnymen", 
      "The Darkness", 
      "Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark", 
      "Funeral for a Friend", 
      "Texas"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English band released the album 'Violator'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Foo Fighters", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Anti-Flag", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "N.W.A.", 
      "The Supremes", 
      "Village People", 
      "The Killers", 
      "The Carpenters", 
      "311"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1995 includes 'Dave Grohl'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "A Button", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Carrot", 
      "Snow", 
      "An Icicle"
    ], 
    "question": "According to the lyrics of the famous Christmas song, what was Frosty The Snowman's nose made from?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "David Bowie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Mika", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "Robbie Williams", 
      "Ed Sheeran", 
      "Kate Bush", 
      "Joe Cocker", 
      "Mark Knopfler", 
      "John Lennon"
    ], 
    "question": "'Alabama Song' was a song by which musician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "R.E.M.", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Counting Crows", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Me First and the Gimme Gimmes", 
      "The Flaming Lips", 
      "Wu-Tang Clan", 
      "The Mothers of Invention", 
      "L.A. Guns", 
      "Nitty Gritty Dirt Band", 
      "Animal Collective"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Peter Buck'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Can The Can", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Do The Do", 
      "See The Sea", 
      "Dance The Dance"
    ], 
    "question": "What Was Suzi Quatro's First Hit In 1973?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nine Inch Nails", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "In This Moment", 
      "Nitty Gritty Dirt Band", 
      "Animal Collective", 
      "Mastodon", 
      "Poco", 
      "Ha*Ash", 
      "Poison", 
      "Avenged Sevenfold", 
      "Live", 
      "Incubus"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American industrial rock band released the studio album 'The Downward Spiral'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Guns N' Roses", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Iced Earth", 
      "Exodus", 
      "Goo Goo Dolls", 
      "Crosby, Stills & Nash", 
      "Daryl Hall & John Oates", 
      "Blackmore's Night"
    ], 
    "question": "'Duff McKagan' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Blondie", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Prince and the Revolution", 
      "Me First and the Gimme Gimmes", 
      "The Flaming Lips", 
      "Poison", 
      "Michael Jackson"
    ], 
    "question": "Whose Albums Included Plastic Letters & Parallel Lines", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pink Floyd", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wings", 
      "Rudimental", 
      "The Alan Parsons Project", 
      "Basement Jaxx", 
      "Spice Girls", 
      "UB40", 
      "Editors", 
      "Duran Duran", 
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Squeeze"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Endless River' was a studio album by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Judas Priest", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arctic Monkeys", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Bring Me the Horizon", 
      "My Dying Bride", 
      "Wet Wet Wet", 
      "Culture Club", 
      "Dire Straits", 
      "Saxon", 
      "Pulp", 
      "Rudimental"
    ], 
    "question": "'Glenn Tipton' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "T. Rex", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Queen", 
      "Talking Heads", 
      "Black Sabbath", 
      "Led Zeppelin"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Released The 70's Album \"Electric Warrior\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals", 
      "Wire"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band performed the compilation album '1'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Spice Girls", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Editors", 
      "Cradle of Filth", 
      "The Sweet", 
      "The Verve", 
      "Hurts", 
      "Bring Me the Horizon", 
      "My Dying Bride", 
      "Wet Wet Wet", 
      "Culture Club", 
      "Dire Straits"
    ], 
    "question": "'Emma Bunton' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "U2", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Public Image Ltd.", 
      "The Script", 
      "The Cure", 
      "Nick Cave and the Bad Seeds", 
      "Siouxsie and the Banshees", 
      "Swans"
    ], 
    "question": "Adam Clayton Plays Bass Guitar For Which Band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Madonna", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "Drake", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Mika", 
      "Aretha Franklin", 
      "Frank Zappa", 
      "George Michael"
    ], 
    "question": "'Rescue Me' was a song by which musician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pink Floyd", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wings", 
      "Rudimental", 
      "The Alan Parsons Project", 
      "Basement Jaxx", 
      "Spice Girls", 
      "UB40", 
      "Editors", 
      "Duran Duran", 
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Squeeze"
    ], 
    "question": "'Nick Mason' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Reed", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Bucket", 
      "The Tap", 
      "The Curl"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Sound Producing Equipment Element Of Many Woodwind Instrument Called?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rihanna", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Drake", 
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Ricky Martin", 
      "Madonna", 
      "will.i.am", 
      "Kylie Minogue", 
      "Bruno Mars", 
      "Ne-Yo", 
      "George Michael", 
      "Michael Jackson"
    ], 
    "question": "'Cheers (Drink to That)' was a song by which Barbadian singer, songwriter, and businesswoman?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Toto", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Styx", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "The Monkees", 
      "Scissor Sisters", 
      "Black Flag", 
      "Journey", 
      "Yellowcard", 
      "Steppenwolf"
    ], 
    "question": "'David Paich' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Weather Report", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Drowning Pool", 
      "Hole", 
      "Type O Negative"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Band Was Formed In The 1970's By Fomer Miles Davis Band Members Joe Zawinul & Wayne Shorter?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Slayer", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Shinedown", 
      "Fleetwood Mac", 
      "Cheap Trick", 
      "Red Hot Chili Peppers", 
      "Chevelle", 
      "Sweetbox"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band released the studio album 'Divine Intervention'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Spice Girls", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Editors", 
      "Cradle of Filth", 
      "The Sweet", 
      "The Verve", 
      "Hurts", 
      "Bring Me the Horizon", 
      "My Dying Bride", 
      "Wet Wet Wet", 
      "Culture Club", 
      "Dire Straits"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1994 includes 'Melanie Brown'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Barbara Streisand", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dolly Parton", 
      "Grace Jones", 
      "Cher"
    ], 
    "question": "Which US Singer Duetted With Donna Summer On The US Number One 'No More Tears'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Michael Jackson", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nicki Minaj", 
      "Neil Young", 
      "Eric Clapton", 
      "Drake", 
      "Alanis Morissette", 
      "Madonna", 
      "Hikaru Utada", 
      "Ludacris", 
      "Janet Jackson", 
      "Beck"
    ], 
    "question": "'Ain't No Sunshine' was a song by which musician?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nightwish", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Haloo Helsinki!", 
      "Hanoi Rocks", 
      "Children of Bodom", 
      "Sonata Arctica", 
      "Rhapsody of Fire", 
      "Stratovarius", 
      "Lordi", 
      "HIM", 
      "Amorphis", 
      "Apocalyptica"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1996 includes 'Tuomas Holopainen'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Joni Mitchell", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Leonard Cohen", 
      "Elton John", 
      "Tom Waits"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Released The 70's Album Entitled \"Blue\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beach Boys", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Swans", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Huey Lewis and the News", 
      "Mudvayne", 
      "De La Soul", 
      "The Four Seasons", 
      "The Everly Brothers", 
      "Rage Against the Machine"
    ], 
    "question": "'Pet Sounds' was a studio album by which American rock band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Iron Maiden", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Squeeze", 
      "Talk Talk", 
      "Goldfrapp", 
      "Camel", 
      "Wings", 
      "Mogwai", 
      "Sade", 
      "Lloyd Cole and the Commotions"
    ], 
    "question": "'Dave Murray' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Shakira\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Enrique Iglesias", 
      "Pitbull", 
      "Jennifer Lopez", 
      "Ricky Martin"
    ], 
    "question": "Who released the album 'Pies Descalzos'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Led Zeppelin", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Lostprophets", 
      "The Kinks", 
      "King Crimson", 
      "Whitesnake", 
      "Gorillaz", 
      "Kaiser Chiefs", 
      "Jethro Tull", 
      "The Yardbirds", 
      "Venom"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band released the song 'Black Dog'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Modern Talking", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sodom", 
      "Rage", 
      "Edguy", 
      "Die Toten Hosen", 
      "Die \u00c4rzte", 
      "Sash!", 
      "Tokio Hotel", 
      "Destruction", 
      "Kraftwerk", 
      "Gregorian"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1984 includes 'Thomas Anders'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Freeway Of Love", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Freedom Freeway", 
      "Freeway Five", 
      "The Respect Freeway"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Freeway Did \"Aretha Franklin\" Sing About?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals", 
      "Wire"
    ], 
    "question": "'The Ballad of John and Yoko' was a song by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Band", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rush", 
      "Crash Test Dummies", 
      "Simple Plan", 
      "Three Days Grace", 
      "The Guess Who", 
      "Billy Talent", 
      "Voivod", 
      "Skinny Puppy", 
      "Barenaked Ladies", 
      "Annihilator"
    ], 
    "question": "'Robbie Robertson' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Best Shot", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rhythm Stick", 
      "Lovin'", 
      "Poison Arrow"
    ], 
    "question": "Pat Benatar Asked You To \"Hit Me With Your ________\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Depeche Mode", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Dead or Alive", 
      "Radiohead", 
      "Iron Maiden", 
      "Oasis", 
      "Echo & the Bunnymen", 
      "The Darkness", 
      "Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark", 
      "Funeral for a Friend", 
      "Texas"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band released the album 'Black Celebration'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Doors", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Styx", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Ratt", 
      "The Cars", 
      "Santana", 
      "Daughtry", 
      "Bowling for Soup"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1965 includes 'Robby Krieger'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rednex", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Cardigans", 
      "Alcazar", 
      "Ace of Base"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Had A One Hit Wonder With \"Cotton Eye Joe\" In 1994\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Queen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals"
    ], 
    "question": "Which British rock band (1970-) released the song 'You're My Best Friend'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Matia Bazar", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Elio e le Storie Tese", 
      "Wess and Dori Ghezzi", 
      "Litfiba", 
      "Lacuna Coil", 
      "Negramaro", 
      "Ricchi e Poveri", 
      "Premiata Forneria Marconi", 
      "Rhapsody of Fire", 
      "Al Bano & Romina Power", 
      "Mod\u00e0"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1975 includes 'Antonella Ruggiero'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Reed", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Bucket", 
      "The Tap", 
      "The Curl"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Sound Producing Equipment Element Of Many Woodwind Instrument Called?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals", 
      "Wire"
    ], 
    "question": "'Let It Be' was a song by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Judas Priest", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arctic Monkeys", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Bring Me the Horizon", 
      "My Dying Bride", 
      "Wet Wet Wet", 
      "Culture Club", 
      "Dire Straits", 
      "Saxon", 
      "Pulp", 
      "Rudimental"
    ], 
    "question": "'Glenn Tipton' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beach Boys", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Swans", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Huey Lewis and the News", 
      "Mudvayne"
    ], 
    "question": "Who Had A Hit With \"Kokomo\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beatles", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals", 
      "Wire"
    ], 
    "question": "Which English rock band released the song 'Please Please Me'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "One Direction", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark", 
      "Blur", 
      "Anathema", 
      "Cradle of Filth", 
      "The Sweet", 
      "The Verve", 
      "Hurts", 
      "Bring Me the Horizon", 
      "My Dying Bride"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band includes 'Harry Styles'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Liverpool", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Manchester", 
      "Newcastle", 
      "Leeds"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Northern UK English city Did The Beatles Come From?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Van Halen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Deep Purple", 
      "The Pussycat Dolls", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Our Lady Peace", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Shinedown", 
      "Fleetwood Mac", 
      "Cheap Trick"
    ], 
    "question": "'Jump' was a song by which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Simon & Garfunkel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "MercyMe", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "REO Speedwagon", 
      "Lifehouse", 
      "The Temptations", 
      "The Used", 
      "Kool & The Gang", 
      "New Found Glory"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1957 includes 'Paul Simon'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ever Fallen In Love", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Smoke on the Water", 
      "Wish You Were Here", 
      "The Boys Are Back In Town"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Classic 70's Hit Features The Line \"And If I Start A Commotion I Run The Risk Of Losing You And That's Worse\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pink Floyd", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Wings", 
      "Rudimental", 
      "The Alan Parsons Project", 
      "Basement Jaxx", 
      "Spice Girls", 
      "UB40", 
      "Editors", 
      "Duran Duran", 
      "Cocteau Twins", 
      "Squeeze"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band performed the compilation album 'The First XI'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fleetwood Mac", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "W.A.S.P.", 
      "Paramore", 
      "Alice in Chains", 
      "Green Day", 
      "Dio", 
      "Blink-182", 
      "Foo Fighters", 
      "Ramones", 
      "My Chemical Romance", 
      "Dropkick Murphys"
    ], 
    "question": "Which band, formed in 1967 includes 'Stevie Nicks'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Meatloaf", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bob Dylan", 
      "David Bowie", 
      "Marvin Gaye"
    ], 
    "question": "Marvin Lee Aday Is The Real Name Of Which Well Known Singer?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Queen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals"
    ], 
    "question": "Which British rock band (1970-) released the song 'Save Me'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Genesis", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark", 
      "Soft Machine", 
      "The Human League", 
      "Asking Alexandria", 
      "Plastic Ono Band", 
      "Frankie Goes to Hollywood", 
      "Heaven 17", 
      "Wham!", 
      "Bad Company", 
      "Madness"
    ], 
    "question": "'Steve Hackett' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mariah Carey", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rihanna", 
      "Beyonce", 
      "Christina Aguilera"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Singing Diva Flopped At The Box Office With Her Debut Movie \u201cGlitter\u201d?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Queen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Level 42", 
      "Deep Purple", 
      "Feeder", 
      "Uriah Heep", 
      "Chumbawamba", 
      "The Rolling Stones", 
      "Coil", 
      "Supergrass", 
      "The Jesus and Mary Chain", 
      "Super Furry Animals"
    ], 
    "question": "Which British rock band (1970-) released the album 'Made in Heaven'?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Daft Punk", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gong", 
      "Indochine", 
      "Nouvelle Vague", 
      "Air", 
      "Superbus", 
      "Kraftwerk", 
      "Depeche Mode", 
      "R\u00f6yksopp", 
      "Basement Jaxx", 
      "Yellow Magic Orchestra"
    ], 
    "question": "'Thomas Bangalter' is a member of which band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "Robert Bell", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mark DuPont", 
      "Lawrence Jones", 
      "Gary Helman"
    ], 
    "question": "What was the real name of Kool, of Kool and the Gang fame?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Music", 
    "correctAnswer": "The Beach Boys", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Swans", 
      "Three 6 Mafia", 
      "The Velvet Underground", 
      "Casting Crowns", 
      "Huey Lewis and the News", 
      "Mudvayne", 
      "De La Soul", 
      "The Four Seasons", 
      "The Everly Brothers", 
      "Rage Against the Machine"
    ], 
    "question": "'Smiley Smile' was a studio album by which American rock band?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }
]
